[energetic music]
[充满活力的音乐]
♪ ♪
♪♪
[laughing evilly]
[邪恶地笑]
[dramatic music]
[戏剧音乐]
♪ ♪
♪♪
Very sloppy, Eugene.
非常马虎，尤金。
Leaving an unprotected
vent that leads
离开不受保护的地方
导致的通风口
right into your office.
直接进入您的办公室。
[laughing evilly]
[邪恶地笑]
Perfect.
完美的。
The secret formula
is as good as mine.
秘密公式
和我的一样好。
Ah!
啊!
I made it.
我做到了。
Yes!
是的！
[humming happily]
[高兴地哼哼]
♪ F is for friends
who do stuff together ♪
♪ F 代表朋友
谁一起做事♪
♪ U is for you and me ♪
♪ U 适合你和我 ♪
[gargling]
[漱口]
♪ N is for anywhere
and anytime at all ♪
♪ N 代表任何地方
任何时候 ♪
Huh?
啊？
[screams]
[尖叫声]
[groaning in pain]
[痛苦呻吟]
♪ Down here
in the deep blue sea ♪
♪ 在这里
在深蓝色的大海里♪
[panting frantically]
[疯狂地喘气]
Aah!
啊啊！
♪ ♪
♪♪
Bubble Bass!
Are you brushing your teeth?
泡泡贝斯！
你在刷牙吗？
Yes, Mother.
是的，妈妈。
Ugh!
啊!
[exhales deeply]
[深呼气]
Oof!
钱币！
Oh, no.
哦，不。
[muffled shouting]
[低声喊叫]
Aah!
啊啊！
[grunts]
[咕哝]
Hmm? Eh, yuck.
唔？呃，恶心。
This place is filthier
than the bathroom
这个地方比较脏
比浴室
in my old fraternity house.
在我的老兄弟会房子里。
Time to get out of here.
是时候离开这里了。
[loud grunting]
[大声咕哝]
[shuddering]
[颤抖]
Terrified,
害怕，
mind blank,
possibly wetting pants.
脑子一片空白，
可能会弄湿裤子。
Wait. I don't wear pants.
等待。我不穿裤子。
Ooh, lucky me.
哦，我很幸运。
[growling]
[咆哮]
[slime bubbling]
[粘液冒泡]
Aah!
啊啊！
That's right.
You better run.
这是正确的。
你最好跑。
Huh?
啊？
[ominous music]
[不祥的音乐]
Terror doubled.
恐怖倍增。
Please!
I'll do whatever you say!
请！
我会照你说的做！
Just don't hurt me!
[sobs]
只是别伤害我！
[抽泣]
We would never hurt the Master.
我们绝不会伤害师父。
[all speaking gibberish]
【全都是胡言乱语】
Wait, what, now?
等等，现在什么？
We are praising you,
我们赞美你，
the Master Creator.
造物主。
Me?
我？
Yes.
是的。
We are C.H.U.M.
我们是 C.H.U.M.
Collective Hive Under Master.
主人领导下的集体蜂巢。
You are Master.
你是师父。
You create us
when you flush chum
你创造了我们
当你冲洗密友时
into sewer
进入下水道
from your upside domain.
来自您的上域。
You mean the Chum Bucket?
你是说密友桶吗？
Yes.
是的。
Chum mixes
with gasses in sewer...
密友混合
下水道里有气体...
[belches loudly]
[大声打嗝]
To form we.
来组成我们。
Goo-goo.
咕咕。
Hmm, makes sense,
嗯，有道理，
huh...
呵呵...
in a stupid sort of way.
以一种愚蠢的方式。
Eh!
呃！
Whoa, what's happening?
哇，发生什么事了？
Master must come to village
师父必须到村里来
so we may worship him.
这样我们就可以敬拜他。
Well, I do love to be worshiped.
嗯，我确实喜欢被崇拜。
Hold on.
How did you recognize me?
坚持，稍等。
你是怎么认出我的？
From sacred scrapbook.
来自神圣的剪贴簿。
Ah!
啊!
We save all articles
about Master
我们保存所有文章
关于师父
that float down here.
漂浮在这里。
Here review of Chum Bucket.
这里回顾一下 Chum Bucket。
You get one negative toilet.
你会得到一个负厕所。
That must be highest
rating possible.
这个应该是最高的
评级可能。
[chuckles]
Yep.
[笑声]
是的。
That's the highest, all right.
这是最高的了，好吧。
[chuckles]
Let's just close that.
[笑声]
让我们结束吧。
[quirky music]
[古怪的音乐]
♪ ♪
♪♪
[grunts]
[咕哝]
♪ ♪
♪♪
Ah!
[grunts]
啊!
[咕哝]
[groaning]
[呻吟]
The Master is pleased
with our village?
师父很高兴
和我们村？
Uh, sure.
Why not?
呃，当然。
为什么不呢？
Oh, thank you, Master.
噢，谢谢师父。
Thank you.
谢谢。
That's enough of that.
这就足够了。
Do you have a napkin
or something
你有餐巾吗
或者什么
I can use to wipe my hands off?
我可以用来擦手吗？
A napkin for Master!
给师父的餐巾纸！
Yuck.
恶心。
Thanks, but try to be
谢谢，但要努力成为
a little faster next time.
下次快一点。
So you C.H.U.M.
would really do anything
所以你C.H.U.M.
真的会做任何事情
for me?
为我？
Yes, yes.
是的，是的。
Whatever the Master wishes.
师父所愿如是。
Wah!
哇！
Hmm, this gives me an idea.
嗯，这给了我一个想法。
I don't need to steal
我不需要偷
the secret Krabby Patty
formula by stealth.
秘密的克拉比帕蒂
隐秘公式。
With you C.H.U.M. by my side,
和你一起 C.H.U.M.在我身边，
I can take it by force!
我可以强行拿下！
Yes, yes.
是的，是的。
Whatever the Master wishes.
师父所愿如是。
Ew. All right, then.
呃。好吧，那么。
Line up for assault training.
列队进行突击训练。
[laughing evilly]
[邪恶地笑]
[bugle playing]
[号角演奏]
In order to successfully
infiltrate the Krusty Krab,
为了成功
渗透到蟹堡王，
you'll need to batter
some doors down.
你需要击打
有些门下来了。
Now get to battering!
现在开始殴打吧！
♪ ♪
♪♪
You call that battering?
你管这叫殴打？
Batter harder.
更用力地击球。
Ah!
啊!
Wait, no, stop!
等等，不，停下来！
How was that, Master?
师父，怎么样？
[groans]
[呻吟]
In order for my plan to succeed,
为了让我的计划能够成功，
you will need
to be expert marksmen.
你会需要
成为专家射手。
Line up and form up.
排队并列队。
♪ ♪
♪♪
[both chattering wildly]
[两人都在疯狂地喋喋不休]
♪ ♪
♪♪
Hold on, hold on.
坚持住，坚持住。
Let me just put up
these targets before you fire.
让我放一下
在你开火之前这些目标。
Master say fire!
师父说火！
- [screams]
- [shouts]
- [尖叫]
- [喊叫]
Uh-oh.
呃哦。
♪ ♪
♪♪
How was our aim, Master?
师父，我们的目标是怎样的？
Eh, impeccable.
嗯，无可挑剔。
When we finally enter
the Krusty Krab,
当我们最终进入
蟹堡王，
you will face an enemy more evil
你将面对一个更邪恶的敌人
than any of you can imagine.
超乎你们的想象。
[all gasp, screaming]
[全都喘气，尖叫]
To get past Krabs
and his vile cronies
为了绕过蟹蟹
和他的卑鄙亲信
and make it
to the secret formula,
并做到
到秘密公式，
you will need to be experts
in the deadly art of karate.
你需要成为专家
在致命的空手道艺术中。
Hoo! Ha! Wah!
呼！哈!哇！
[grunting violently]
[剧烈地咕哝]
Now show Master what you got.
现在让师父看看你得到了什么。
A-plus.
[sighs]
A+。
[叹气]
You're ready.
[sighs]
你准备好了。
[叹气]
Ay!
哎呀！
[humming happily]
[高兴地哼哼]
- Hello, Eugene.
- Plankton?
- 你好，尤金。
- 浮游生物？
Ah, get out of here
before I flush you.
啊，离开这里
在我冲洗你之前。
The only thing getting
flushed around here
唯一得到的就是
在这里泛红
are your hopes
of the Krabby Patty formula
是你的希望
蟹黄饼配方
not being stolen by me!
没有被我偷走！
Huh, you and what army?
呃，你和什么军队？
Me and my C.H.U.M. army.
我和我的 C.H.U.M.军队。
[gasps]
[喘气]
[laughing evilly]
[邪恶地笑]
Plankton, what insanity is this?
浮游生物，这是什么疯子？
The insanity of genius!
天才的疯狂！
What's that chum doing?
那个朋友在做什么？
Anything I want it to.
我想要什么都可以。
[laughing evilly]
[邪恶地笑]
[suspenseful music]
[悬疑音乐]
♪ ♪
♪♪
Oh, Krabs.
哦，蟹蟹。
You look a little hungry.
你看起来有点饿了。
Give him a taste, boys.
孩子们，让他尝尝吧。
Ha, ha, ha!
哈哈哈！
[grunting]
[咕噜声]
[shouting]
[喊叫]
- [humming]
- SpongeBob! SpongeBob!
- [嗡嗡声]
- 海绵宝宝！海绵宝宝！
[vocalizing]
[发声]
♪ ♪
♪♪
You'll never get me formula.
你永远不会给我配方。
Today your formula.
今天你的公式。
Tomorrow the world.
明天的世界。
You can't hide forever, Krabs.
你不能永远隐藏，蟹蟹。
Come meet your stinky fate.
来迎接你的臭命运吧。
[laughing evilly]
[邪恶地笑]
Sorry, Krabs.
对不起，蟹蟹。
Your aging acrobatics
are no match
你的衰老杂技
不匹配
for my C.H.U.M. monster.
为了我的 C.H.U.M.怪物。
[giggles]
[咯咯笑]
So long, suckers.
再见，傻瓜们。
Ah!
啊!
Oh, shrimp!
噢，虾！
Attack!
攻击！
My putrescent platoon!
我腐烂的排！
Eat splinters, ugly!
吃碎片，丑！
Oh!
哦！
Whoa!
哇！
♪ ♪
♪♪
[upbeat music playing
on headphones]
[欢快的音乐响起
在耳机上]
Oh!
哦！
This is your
last chance, Eugene.
这是你的
最后一次机会，尤金。
Give up the formula or else!
放弃公式，否则！
Or else what?
不然又怎样？
Gah!
- Whoa!
嘎！
- 哇！
Or else this!
不然这个！
All right, all right,
I'll give you what you want.
好吧，好吧，
我会给你你想要的。
Just please don't hurt me.
只是请不要伤害我。
SpongeBob, help!
海绵宝宝，救命啊！
[monster growling]
- SpongeBob!
[怪物咆哮]
- 海绵宝宝！
Stop him!
阻止他！
Ooh, a penny!
哦，一分钱！
Not again.
不会再有。
Ah!
啊!
Oh!
哦！
I'm so sorry, Mr. Krabs.
我很抱歉，蟹老板。
My little hero!
我的小英雄！
Mwah!
哇！
Ooh.
[giggles]
哦。
[咯咯笑]
Well, thanks for trying, anyway.
好吧，无论如何，谢谢你的尝试。
So, uh,
所以，呃，
you guys want to hang out,
you know,
你们想出去玩，
你知道，
maybe worship me a little more.
也许更崇拜我一点。
No, we think C.H.U.M.
happier in the sewer.
不，我们认为 C.H.U.M.
下水道里更快乐。
Too crazy up here.
这里太疯狂了。
But you'll keep
worshipping me, right?
但你会保留
崇拜我吧？
We check our schedule.
我们检查我们的日程安排。
Get back to you.
回到你身边。
[toilet flushes]
- Aw.
[厕所冲水]
- 噢。